THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS
AI-GENERATED CONTENT
YOON JAEMIN
[player] Hey, Lee Hyunsoo!
Think you can catch this?
[gasps]
[sobbing]
[theme music playing]
MURDER CLUB: LIAR'S TABLE
Isn't that the director?
[Kang Dohyun] That's him, right?
- Yeah, it is.
- It is.
- Oh jeez, the director…
- He's the culprit.
[Kang Dohyun] What's going on here?
It looks like a family photo.
Oh, there are multiple CCTVs.
Let's see.
JO HAJUN BUYS A CAKE?
To be honest, it caught me off guard.
It happened to be me,
so I turned it off instantly.
But the truth is,
I was the one who ordered the cake.
It was me.
I ordered a special custom cake
with the aim of targeting Park Taeo.
It all lines up. This is conclusive proof.
All right. Director.
- You're back.
- If you look here,
there's a torn-up photo with you in it.
- [Kim Doyun] Can you explain this photo?
- [Kang Dohyun] Look. Right here.
- Can you explain it?
- It's you, isn't it?
- [Jo Hajun] Oh, this.
- Yeah.
It's our parent company.
It's the Geumseong Group chairman
and his family.
- Why did you rip it?
- Why take a photo together?
I don't know if I should say…
Fess up right now!
He's the youngest son of a chaebol family.
Spill, already! Explain this.
- He's a chaebol's son.
- You're the culprit, aren't you?
Don't just laugh.
- Wait.
- You rotten bastard!
Wait, Dohyun.
You're very worked up right now.
He raised his hand.
[Kim Doyun] Hear me out.
- The truth is…
- Yes?
…I'm the director
of the PR Strategy Team, right?
These people are actually
- my family.
- [Kim Doyun] I knew it.
My father's the chairman.
I thought so.
Oh, you're the chairman's son.
JO HAJUN IS THE YOUNGEST SON
OF A CHAEBOL FAMILY
- [Kim Doyun] Director.
- Yes?
It turns out you're the son
of a chaebol family.
But during my private conversation
with Pani earlier… I mean--
- Coach Yoon.
- [Kim Doyun] Okay.
I had a private conversation
with the coach,
and he said you didn't have much motive
for killing Park Taeo.
- Why kill someone for a canceled advert?
- Right.
- That's what the coach said.
- Yeah.
Do you agree with that?
Of course, you shouldn't kill someone
over a canceled advert.
But based on the information I have,
the promotion campaign
was career-defining for you
and played a major role
in your performance evaluation,
so it was a key factor
in deciding the succession.
So if this campaign fell through,
he would be ruined.
- For failing to deliver.
- You'd be out of the running.
You were aiming high, huh?
- No way.
- [Yoon Minseok] The card I took
from the director
stated that his life depended on it.
That's what he said
in his unsent text to Park Taeo.
He said his life depended
on this campaign.
Hear me out.
When trying to get players on board…
Come on, you know how it goes.
- "Help me out this once."
- [players laughing]
"Please. Just this once."
"Hyunsoo, don't change teams.
Come back to Seoul."
You say things like this.
I had no idea,
but he's the chairman's son.
As it turns out,
he was pushed out
of the race for succession.
THE CAMPAIGN WAS KEY
TO HIS SUCCESSION
So, who would he resent the most?
The late Park Taeo.
He claims he said this and that
to sweet-talk Taeo into collaborating,
but it's hardly likely.
He probably swore at him
and showed his true colors.
You might not have been so nice.
"Think you're a big man?"
- Yeah, I can see that.
- He might've threatened him.
"You think you're still a big shot?"
"What a joke. I'm the one
who made you a star."
- You keep--
- "Your success has gone to your head."
"How dare you act so big?"
"You ungrateful jerk."
Maybe you lost your temper.
Which era are you living in?
You can't do that in this day and age.
I'm really sorry to interrupt,
- but we don't have much time.
- Right.
We need to check the CCTV,
so let's move on.
- Good idea.
- First, Dohyun--
- I took a card from Lee Hyunsoo.
- Okay.
- You wrote in your training log…
…"We had different starts."
"If it wasn't for that ball…"
- He felt inferior.
- Yeah.
- There were a lot of entries like that.
- He was jealous.
DID HE ENVY AND ADMIRE TAEO?
[Kang Dohyun] There was a ball
at the crime scene.
And the last
conclusive piece of evidence--
- I'll check out the CCTV.
- Okay.
Hang on.
Dohyun talks too much.
HAJUN HEADS TO THE CCTV ZONE AGAIN
I also took a card from Lee Hyunsoo,
and it was also about his jealousy.
- The king of jealousy.
- Yeah. The rundown is,
the Major League teams
were looking to sign Taeo first,
but there was talk about signing Hyunsoo.
- [exclaims]
- It was being discussed, but…
Well, it's a really long story,
but I had a son.
A SON?
- You had a son?
- [Yoon Minseok] Yes.
- That was random.
- I had a son.
- Suddenly?
- Dohyun knows.
Of course, I know.
- I had a son, but he died.
- Okay.
Who killed him?
[Yoon Minseok] I didn't know,
but my son's name
was Yoon Jaemin.
But the Major League teams
put their consideration
of Lee Hyunsoo on hold
because of his connection
to my son's death.
That's what the card said.
I can explain exactly what happened.
Can you?
- What happened?
- You know I'm the king of jealousy.
When I was on the youth team,
Park Taeo threw a ball at me
as a way of taunting me.
Due to my burning jealousy,
I snapped and whacked it back hard,
but the ball flew in the direction
of Jaemin, the coach's son.
SHOCK
My son…
- It was reckless intent.
- [Yoon Minseok] Right.
- How awful.
- How could you take a life like that?
[Lee Hyunsoo] Following that incident,
Park Taeo was cleared
of any connection to the tragedy.
- [Yoon Minseok] So you were the only--
- Yes, I took all the blame.
Hold on. Then, you must
bear a grudge too, Coach.
But I didn't know who was responsible.
- How can you not know?
- He confessed that he was involved.
- Here's why I didn't know.
- Okay.
I was in complete despair at the time.
Also, it was an incident involving
the Saints youth team,
so I didn't press the issue.
Of course, I was devastated.
- You didn't dig into why your son died?
- [Kang Dohyun] Right?
That's what it says here!
That's what it says!
- It makes no sense.
- Don't ask me!
- I don't get it either!
- Your son died, yet you're here laughing.
SOBBING
Something's wrong with him.
- My Jaemin!
- Is this normal?
How can he sit here laughing
when his son died?
You killed him? It was you?
[Kim Doyun] I don't understand
how the coach could be in the dark
about who killed his son
and even how he died.
I don't know.
It's only getting more confusing.
I'm certain that Lee Hyunsoo
isn't the culprit in this case.
As for the death of Yoon Jaemin,
it was an honest mistake.
It was an unfortunate accident.
But Park Taeo and Lee Hyunsoo
were responsible for killing my son.
I think that much is true.
This bastard is the reason my son died,
but I don't think he's connected
to this murder case.
I brought this.
HYUNSOO BROUGHT AN OBJECT CLUE
- It's the fan club's ledger.
- Okay.
- [Lee Hyunsoo] It shows Doyun knew the
- details and severity of Taeo's illness.
We saw that earlier,
and this is further proof.
It's a ledger that focuses
only on Park Taeo.
LOOKING AROUND
- Furthermore, on a computer…
- "Five thousand won."
…he wrote a private post
about wanting to get married.
I knew it.
They dated.
You're right.
- No, we didn't. This is…
- That's right.
- What do you mean?
- The fan club.
- The fan club--
- This guy…
You may be behind the times,
- but marriage is possible now.
- That's not it.
- Surprisingly, it can happen.
- Who can get married?
It's too far-fetched.
- Same-sex marriage?
- [players] Yes.
That's what it says on the card I took.
You did write a private post, right?
- Who knew this was a possibility?
- This is why he became
the president of a fan club.
I'm into women.
That's true in real life
and for my character, Doyun.
Why would he like men?
Of course, I respect people's preferences,
but I'm not personally inclined that way.
It's too much of a stretch, isn't it?
I don't think it makes any sense
that I killed him because I loved him.
[Lee Hyunsoo] It says here precisely…
It says the post was written
by Kim Doyeon.
The name…
My name is spelled "yun."
- What's up with that?
- It was written by a Kim Doyeon?
- I saw that name…
- The name is--
-…on a card.
- Mine's "yun."
ROUND 1:
TAEO FANDOM ANALYSIS REPORT
WRITTEN BY DOYEON, SENT TO HAJUN
Who's Doyeon?
This is strange. It says Doyeon.
I saw that name earlier.
Director Jo mentioned--
HAJUN CHECKS THE CCTV AGAIN
Let's take a look again. 31FE.
Oh, he was shooting a documentary,
so it was even more crucial
to keep his secrets under wraps.
Got it.
Either the coach or the manager.
Then the prime suspects…
Where have you been, Director?
CURIOUS
I just checked the CCTV.
- I saw related footage.
- Okay.
[Jo Hajun] It was a documentary
with an absurd title.
What was it?
"The Legendary Kang Dohyun."
- Me?
- That's right.
ME AGAIN?
It's not me.
You need to stop
barking up the wrong tree.
Hear me out.
He's not just a manager,
but "a legendary manager."
- He called himself that?
- [Kang Dohyun] Since I was young,
- I dreamed of that.
- All right, I have something to share.
I found conclusive proof.
"Kang Dohyun's kickback envelope."
It's a document about his kickbacks.
Look at the name.
- It's the "legendary" Kang Dohyun.
- Okay.
- He's a very messed-up guy.
- [Kang Dohyun] No, I'm not.
- Jeez.
- What do you think of this?
- No, listen.
- Can you explain it?
The word "kickback" is a bit misleading.
It's not a kickback.
It's a sponsorship.
It's management costs.
Meeting reporters off the record
and things like that can be quite costly.
In that case, did the hundred million won
that the director embezzled
go into your pockets, Dohyun?
- [Kim Doyun] Then it's all connected.
- Oh, you mean me?
HAJUN EMBEZZLED MONEY?
What are you talking about?
That's ridiculous.
[sighs]
Who are these people?
ASSEMBLYMAN CHEOL MEETS PRIVATELY
WITH GEUMSEONG CHAIRMAN
- There's someone called Cheol Ongsik.
- I saw that name too!
[Kang Dohyun] Cheol Ongsik?
He's just an assemblyman.
- Why is he involved with you?
- An assemblyman?
- He's a huge fan of our team.
- How is he connected?
- What about it?
- That's why we're close.
- He's one of our nation's representatives.
- Wait.
If someone bribes a public official
with a hundred million won,
- that's a big deal, right?
- It's huge. You go straight to jail.
The manager should be
immediately arrested.
You sent him a hundred million won first.
I knew the assemblyman,
but I never bribed him.
For goodness' sake. What are you on about?
ROUND 3 CARD CLUES:
INTERNAL REPORT,
TRAINING LOG, EMAIL,
FAN CLUB PRIVATE POST
- Did you really not know?
- What?
- Honestly?
- Know what?
Just say you knew. I'll believe you more.
- Oh, you mean who killed my son?
- Yeah.
I'd be more convinced that you're innocent
if you knew Park Taeo killed your son
because you kept that to yourself
for all these years.
You were still his coach despite that.
So I don't think it's noteworthy.
But you not knowing
how your son died is a bit…
I honestly didn't look into it
after his death.
- Here's why.
- Okay.
It happened on the Saints youth team,
- and I didn't want to expose my own club.
- Mmm.
Pressing the matter
wouldn't bring my son back,
so I didn't dig deeper.
My top suspect is still the manager.
Look at this.
Park Taeo was going to expose
the club's corruption, right?
I think it was connected
to the assemblyman and Geumseong Group.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
The hundred million won
on the secret ledger.
Right, yes.
You sent it to the manager, right?
Honestly speaking,
you could've sent him the money
to bring in officials
like the assemblyman.
Okay, I'll be honest, Hyunsoo.
The parent company
run by my father, the chairman,
ordered me to deliver the money,
so I just did as I was told.
How much it was and what it was used for
is beyond my knowledge.
- My second suspect is the director.
- [Yoon Minseok] Right.
Do you remember how I kept asking him
if he recalled the cake?
I have a question for you.
What do you think about the cake?
- The cake?
- Yes. What are your thoughts on it?
It was a congratulatory party,
so it's only natural
there was champagne and a cake.
The director got me to deliver that cake.
THE FAN CLUB PRESIDENT
DELIVERED THE CAKE?
He made me deliver the cake.
But this is a secret
because I plan to confront him
about it at the discussion table.
Here's what I'm wondering.
We don't know the exact cause of death.
He was hit by a bat,
but he could've been killed
some other way first
and then hit with the bat afterward
- to make it seem like the murder weapon.
- Right.
And that's why the culprit used my bat.
You really never hit him?
Even if you didn't kill him,
you never even smacked his bum?
- No, I didn't.
- Really?
- You're sure?
- I never hit him.
It's almost impossible to kill
a sturdy baseball player with a bat
without him fighting back.
But if someone got a cake
to make it easier to kill him,
it must be either the director
or the fan club president.
But I'm not sure which one.
It's too hard to tell.
[host] Here is the fourth shared clue.
- The fan club president's insulin.
- [Kang Dohyun] Right.
For managing his glucose.
- This.
- But it's not been used.
- It's new.
- It's not been used?
[Yoon Minseok] I think someone tossed it
before it could be used.
SOMEONE THREW IT AWAY?
I'll take a card from the coach,
who's got more secrets than I thought.
I'll take the manager's last card
to seal the case against him.
Are you that upset with me?
Sorry. It's not because I doubt you.
- You should just take mine…
- [Kang Dohyun] Sure.
…since it's my last one.
Since this insulin
is pretty strong evidence…
But I also need to look into the director.
These are our last card clues, right?
COLLECTING OBJECT CLUES
- We searched these.
- I got the one from locker one.
We didn't check locker six.
Found it.
I have a record in my hand.
It seems the fan club president
has a VIP entry pass.
We both got one.
How can a fan club president
have a VIP pass?
The record shows an entry at 11 p.m.
But why did you enter again at midnight?
- I didn't go back in at midnight.
- What? Midnight?
Did you cross paths with Park Taeo?
I met him at 11:05 p.m.
- You met him at 11:05 p.m.?
- Yes.
You checked in with your pass?
No, 11:05… I'll explain exactly.
- I met the director at 10:50 p.m.…
- Okay.
…and he told me to deliver
the cake to the locker room.
That's right. It was around that time.
But why didn't you
disclose that right away?
You didn't mention the cake.
The cake isn't very important.
- Anyway--
- It keeps coming up as evidence.
- [Yoon Minseok] So you delivered the cake?
- I delivered it.
- What time?
- [Kim Doyun] At 11:05 p.m.
- 11:05 p.m.?
- I delivered the cake at 11:05 p.m.
and left five minutes later.
I was only there for five minutes.
But on my way out,
I saw Lee Hyunsoo.
DOYUN AND HYUNSOO CROSSED PATHS
OUTSIDE THE LOCKERS
- We crossed paths, right?
- Yeah, we did.
- Taeo was alive until then.
- Yes.
- Our Taeo was still alive until then.
- You didn't go back in at midnight?
"Our Taeo"?
- That's very suspicious.
- He's our player.
Who has the most information
out of all of us?
When the ace player
went into hypoglycemic shock,
I think the only person
who knew his condition inside out
was the fan club president,
so he's the top suspect.
But we need to investigate
to see if that's true.
If this confirms it,
then it's case closed.
Who's that?
It's CCTV footage of the stadium.
He was about to expose something to do
with the assemblyman.
- Oh, you're right.
- That's not it.
- I just checked the CCTV.
- Yes?
What time did you say
you went home earlier?
- When did you leave the stadium?
- 11 p.m.
- No, at 11:05 p.m.…
- Yes?
-…I delivered the cake and ran into you.
- Yeah.
And when I left,
- it was around midnight.
- Midnight?
- Can I check quickly?
- But…
- Hold on.
- [Lee Hyunsoo] But the CCTV footage showed
you were there at 2:17 a.m.,
- looking right at the camera.
- [players exclaim]
- Wait a minute.
- I've got chills.
- It was 2 a.m.?
- It was 2:17 a.m.
- I've got chills.
- The culprit reappeared at the scene.
HYUNSOO MISREAD 12:02 A.M.
AS 02:02 A.M.
Your alibi is totally…
- You lunatic!
- [Jo Hajun] Wait.
- It was 12:17 a.m.
- Wait.
You little!
Why did you hit me?
HE GOT SLAPPED
I mean…
He got physical!
[Kim Doyun] Why did you do that?
Why did you hit me?
- I'm sorry.
- What the heck?
I got riled up.
This must be how you killed Park Taeo!
He beat him to death like this.
It was forceful enough to kill someone.
That's how he killed him.
- Hold on.
- I'm sorry.
Hang on.
That's not right. I went back at 2 a.m.?
It was 12:07 a.m.
Yeah, it was close to midnight.
It was just past it.
ROUND 4 CARD CLUES
NEWS ARTICLE, COACH'S ACCESS
PASS, STADIUM ACCESS RECORD,
DRIVER'S LICENSE,
DOCUMENTARY CONTRACT
[host] Round 4 is over.
It is time for the private conversations.
You've been through a lot, Director.
After delivering the cake,
why did you linger around afterward?
When did I linger?
Did you really not see Park Taeo again
after delivering the cake?
Not after I delivered the cake.
Between 11 p.m. and midnight,
the estimated time of the crime,
- the only one who met Park Taeo for sure…
- That's right.
-…the only one with an alibi is…
- Yeah, it's me.
- It's you.
- Yeah.
But I bumped into Lee Hyunsoo
on my way out,
and he went in after me.
The players were celebrating together,
so it makes sense he was there.
My point is that Park Taeo was alive.
I just delivered the cake then left.
He was either still alive
or he was already dead,
but Lee Hyunsoo is playing dumb.
No. You can't accuse me like this.
- Why not?
- Because it was a bit suspicious
- that you got me to deliver the cake.
- Right.
- The cake was the centerpiece.
- Yeah.
- It looked like the whole thing was eaten.
- It was.
So I wondered
if it had been laced with pills.
You think I put something in it?
It'd make sense if he fainted
due to low blood sugar.
- But I didn't suspect you.
- Right.
- But if you suspect me like this…
- No, no.
- No, listen.
- That's a bit upsetting.
- Look.
- You get me, right?
Then let me just ask you
one last question.
Do you know when Park Taeo
needed to take medication or get injected?
Do you know his treatment schedule?
I don't know the exact times
he needed his injection.
I just know that he needed injections.
But you don't know the time frame?
Time frame?
- Me?
- Yeah.
No, I don't.
We're looking for the killer,
so we need proof that they used
the insulin shot somehow.
- We can connect it to the director's cake…
- Yeah.
…and the fan club president said
he went around with the cake.
Do we think there's a twist or…
- Or do we think by the book?
- Exactly.
We're focusing too much
on just the director.
This is so hard.
[host] Here is the final shared clue.
[Lee Hyunsoo] At last.
- If only we got it sooner.
- [Jo Hajun] It's the conclusive proof.
"The immediate cause of death
was intracranial hemorrhage
and brain injury
due to blunt head trauma."
"The antecedent cause
was altered consciousness
due to acute hypoglycemic shock."
"The underlying cause
was metabolic abnormality due to fasting,
dehydration,
and excessive alcohol consumption."
There are three causes of death?
- The immediate cause points to the killer.
- Right.
I think the blunt trauma
was caused by the bat.
- He hit him with the bat first.
- Yeah.
Park Taeo didn't take medication
for hypoglycemic shock before that?
Who made the cake again?
- It was made by our director.
- No, hold on.
I didn't make the cake.
- Yes, you did.
- I delivered it.
I'm a director, not a baker.
- Okay, you delivered it.
- I did.
Where did you buy it from?
I got a subordinate
to go and buy the cake.
[Yoon Minseok] Here's the conclusion.
If you have low blood sugar,
eating cake raises it back to normal.
- Right?
- Usually, yes.
But to prevent that,
instead of using sugar,
the culprit may have used
a substitute like Stevia.
Normally, eating the cake
should lead to a blood sugar spike,
but because it didn't,
it led to hypoglycemic shock.
Or the culprit might've
masked the taste of alcohol
- so he drank it without knowing.
- Could be why he drank excessively.
This was planned
by the person who made the cake.
But if it's someone who could
bake a cake with all that in mind,
the only one who fits the bill
is the fan club president.
- He's the only one with that knowledge.
- But it was given to him
- by the director.
- That's not it.
He just passed on the cake.
- You think he switched the cakes?
- Yeah.
-He swapped it.
- Wait.
- No, I didn't.
- The cake didn't kill him.
We know now that the cake didn't kill him.
So I think that makes
the cake more important
because after it was delivered,
the VIP pass was used
one more time, right?
So he knew that the cake
would make Park Taeo faint,
and he went back to finish him off
by using the VIP card for access.
To add to what he just said,
Kim Doyun, the fan club president,
knew that between 11 p.m. and 11:30 p.m.,
Park Taeo had to take the insulin shot
or it could badly affect his health.
- He knew that from the start.
- Yeah.
I knew that he needed
to manage his glucose levels.
Here's the thing. It's common knowledge
among the fan club members.
When I asked the fan club president,
he said he didn't know
the exact time frame,
but he changed his story.
I think Kim Doyun
had more than enough time to kill Taeo.
- I'm going to check the CCTV.
- Sure.
There will probably be CCTV footage of me.
I'm just giving you a heads up.
- All of a sudden?
- Hear me out.
- He's laying the groundwork.
- Here's why I'm telling you.
I shouldn't say this,
but I really want to catch the culprit.
I actually went into the locker room.
What?
"D, S, H, E."
D, S, H, E.
What's this?
DASHCAM FOOTAGE?
SD CARD MISSING
To be honest, I planned to kill Park Taeo.
- [gasps]
- [Yoon Minseok] But when I entered,
I found that he was
already dead.
I'm bringing this up now
because it might help solve the case.
I'm not supposed to reveal this.
- Right.
- I'm not meant to reveal it,
but if I keep it to myself,
you'll think I'm the culprit,
so I'm telling you
to save you the confusion.
I actually went into the locker room,
and I even had a bat ready to kill Taeo,
but he was already dead.
Why didn't I report it?
I suspected that he was responsible
for my son's death,
so I thought he was justly punished.
He got what he deserved,
so I didn't report it.
- That's cold.
- But I didn't kill him.
I think the cake was used
by the director or the fan club president
just to knock him out,
but they didn't kill him.
It was someone else.
We're looking for the person
who caused the blunt head trauma.
I was suspicious of the director
and the fan club president.
- Suddenly?
- Just like me,
you both intended to kill him,
- but someone else actually did it.
- You're getting out of it like this?
It's not very believable.
Coach Yoon is a very smart man.
He's very sly.
His son died,
so it was a father's revenge.
I somewhat understand it,
but he shouldn't have done that.
I think it was a very calculated excuse.
Thinking about it now,
he might not have been dead
when I saw him.
You saw him dead?
- While you were checking out the CCTV--
- Yeah, I missed it.
- When I saw him--
- What time?
It was around 11:30 p.m.
It was sometime
between 11 p.m. and 12 a.m.
- I went there to kill him.
- Okay.
- But--
- You planned to kill him?
That's what he said.
I'm not meant to reveal that,
so why did I?
Why would I share such crucial evidence?
Because I'm not guilty.
I was going to kill him,
so I headed over with my bat,
but he was already unconscious.
But that was just the result
of his primary and secondary injuries.
I found him unconscious
due to hypoglycemic shock,
and whoever went in after I left
might be the one who killed him.
You didn't hit him?
No, I didn't.
- And you didn't feed him anything?
- No, I never saw the cake before today.
Let me share what I found.
Do you like driving, Coach Yoon?
- Driving?
- Yes.
I don't drive.
- What?
- I don't drive.
- You're unlicensed?
- You have no license?
I do, but I don't drive.
Why not if you have a license?
I'll explain.
The statute of limitations has expired
for his hit-and-run crime.
The expiry time and date
were 11 p.m. on October 31, 2025.
Remember the dates that were crossed out?
It was the expiry date.
-Why did you count down until that day?
- [Yoon Minseok] Hear me out.
It's not very relevant to this case.
I didn't want to waste time
on something pointless.
- But I'm curious.
- I'll explain.
Park Taeo killed my son many years ago.
- Yes.
- It was involuntary manslaughter.
Manager Kang Dohyun suggested
we get a drink, so I had a few drinks.
-I have no memory of the event…
- Okay.
…but I hit someone while driving.
I killed someone.
- Due to drink driving?
- Yes.
- Why didn't you tell us that?
- It wasn't necessary.
It's irrelevant to this case.
I didn't bring it up
- because it's not related to Taeo's death.
- It is relevant.
He found out your secret.
DID TAEO WITNESS
THE HIT-AND-RUN?
He questioned you about it,
so you got angry
because you were waiting
for the statute of limitations to expire.
You were just one day away from freedom.
That wasn't in my guide.
- Is that why--
- What on earth?
Is that why you resolved
to kill him right away?
As I told you earlier,
I was planning to kill him.
I even had a bat ready.
But he was already knocked out.
- Taeo was attacked in the locker room.
- What he's saying is…
- It's conclusive.
- He had two sets of injuries.
But he was killed by a third injury.
Here's what I think.
The large pool of blood
- formed while he was still alive, right?
- Yeah.
That's when I walked in
and saw him unconscious.
I thought he was dead,
so I turned around and left.
But I think he died after that.
I honestly think someone else
delivered the fatal blow.
From a logical standpoint,
one person walked in on him alive,
and another found him dead.
One of them must be the killer.
It must be Hyunsoo or the coach,
who went in after me.
- Doyun.
- Yes?
Did you know about Park Taeo's girlfriend?
- Park Taeo's girlfriend? Yes, I knew.
- Yes.
- You knew?
- What?
- Did that upset you?
- Taeo's girlfriend?
- His girlfriend…
What are you talking about?
He cheated.
You liked Park Taeo, didn't you?
[laughter]
- This is…
- Listen.
[Kim Doyun] I'm sorry, but…
Don't hit me. Hear me out.
Why would I hit you for having a crush?
Here's the thing.
- Granted, in this roleplay…
- Am I right?
…my character's a bit random.
- That said…
- Yes?
…I don't think they would
move the story in that direction.
I can acknowledge everything else,
but I'm the only one without a motive.
You felt the most betrayed
since he didn't love you back.
Some fans think players should
only focus on their career
instead of being distracted
by dating and marriage.
Then was his girlfriend
your younger sister?
WAS TAEO'S GIRLFRIEND
DOYUN'S YOUNGER SISTER?
[Lee Hyunsoo] Park Taeo's girlfriend.
The fan club ledger we saw earlier
was written by Kim Doyeon.
And your name is Kim Doyun.
Isn't that a bit of a stretch?
How so?
The name "Doyeon"
has appeared a few times.
I don't have a younger sibling.
I'm an only child.
- You seem to be hiding something.
- [Kim Doyun] I'm not.
You seem to be hiding something
whenever we come back to this topic.
Not at all.
You seem to keep changing the topic.
I don't know if I should say this, but--
You keep turning it around on me.
We're not trying to pin it on you.
- Let me share what I know.
- Okay.
- The name is Kim Doyeon, right?
- Yes.
- Kim Doyeon.
- She's actually someone I know.
- Ah.
[Jo Hajun] Kim Doyeon.
- We went to middle school together.
- Okay.
Kim Doyeon.
Based on the information I know,
you're her older brother.
What?
Are you Doyeon's brother?
- No. I don't have a sister.
- Is she your younger sister?
- What?
- I don't have a sister.
- Who's lying?
- Are you in your right mind?
- Someone's lying.
- I'm not.
Are you lying right now?
- You do have a sister!
- Come on.
- I really don't.
- Hang on.
She was my schoolmate.
-We went to school together.
- Okay.
DID KIM DOYEON AND JO HAJUN
GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL?
- From what I know…
- Yes?
…Kim Doyeon was the original
president of the fan club.
DOYEON WAS
THE ORIGINAL PRESIDENT?
- She was the original president.
- Yes.
I don't know if I should say this,
but Kim Doyeon died.
FORMER PRESIDENT IS DEAD?
- She died, and--
- Why are there so many dead people?
It's my understanding
that the person who took over
as the new president of the fan club
was Kim Doyun.
So what was your relationship with her?
Doyeon and I went to the same school.
When I was first assigned
to the promotion campaign,
she recommended Park Taeo
and connected me to him.
But for some unknown reason,
she took her own life.
Someone with a similar name
suddenly took over
as president of the same fan club.
It's so strange that he was
her immediate successor.
You knew that Park Taeo
had something to do
with the death of the first president
of the fan club.
[Kim Doyun] Mmm.
Then I guess the private post
could've been written by Kim Doyeon.
- It seems like we all had a motive.
- Yeah.
We all had a motive.
- We all have a story.
- What's more important
is who struck Taeo last.
If we focus on the timing,
- you went in as I left, right?
- Yeah.
- That was around 11:05 p.m., right?
- Yes.
When did you say you left?
I went in at 11:05 p.m.
and left about 15 minutes later.
What time did you say you went in?
- Be honest.
- It was 11:30 p.m.
So between 11:15 and 11:30 p.m.,
Park Taeo was knocked out.
- Right?
- Yeah, however it happened.
Right. I thought he was dead,
but whether he was actually dead
or if he was just struck
and fainted from hypoglycemia
- is undetermined.
- We don't know exactly.
But we know for sure that he was
knocked out because he was hit
- or because he ate the cake.
- He was struck.
- He definitely ate the cake.
- Right.
Whether it was the cake or a beating
or his head slamming into something,
- we know it happened in the locker room.
- Yes.
Then aren't you the prime suspect?
Wait. Hear me out. The reason I told you--
So whether he's lying or--
I didn't need to tell you,
and I knew you would suspect me,
but I told you anyway
because it was the only way
you'd know for sure it wasn't me.
He was unconscious when I found him,
so he was either already dead or…
I thought he was dead.
But seeing this made me think
he might've died later.
And I shared what should've been a secret
to make that point.
- So when it comes to suspecting--
- [timer beeping]
- What?
- Is that the end?
Does that mean we're screwed?
You were all convinced it was me
at the start.
- What the heck?
- [Kang Dohyun] Talk about ridiculous.
I think the manager
got into a fight with Taeo.
[host] Before voting,
please make your closing arguments.
- Sure, I'm not entirely innocent.
- [players laughing]
I've committed a few blunders.
But I've been wrongly accused.
I'm not the killer.
You may suspect me because of the cake,
but you saw the medical record earlier.
Can the immediate cause of death
be attributed to me?
I did plan to kill him, but I didn't.
I never even hit him.
I think the answer
lies in the time of his death.
I want you to look for the person
who could've been there at that time.
I'll pass.
You don't need to defend yourself, huh?
The fan club president is Kim Doyun,
but there was a Kim Doyeon.
I figured it could be related
to a sibling connection,
so the fan club president
was my prime suspect until the end.
I think I'm leaning towards the coach
as my final guess
because the timeline
makes him the most likely suspect.
Coach Yoon isn't a big guy,
so he weakened Taeo with the cake,
then struck him with the bat.
As awful as it is,
I think that's how it went down.
VOTING COMPLETE
[host] Here are the voting results.
Kang Dohyun got zero votes,
Lee Hyunsoo got zero votes,
Jo Hajun got zero votes,
Yoon Minseok got two votes,
and Kim Doyun got three votes.
Kim Doyun got the most votes.
SIGH
[host] The selected player shall open
the ending box bearing their number
and read the ending scenario aloud.
I can't believe you're making me
do something so humiliating.
"Doyun insisted it was revenge
for his younger sister, Doyeon."
"After losing his parents in a car crash,
the only family he had left was Doyeon."
"When he found out that Park Taeo
had abandoned his sister,
he made up his mind to get revenge."
"Jo Hajun's victory cake,
the insulin and glucose
discarded by the manager,
and Lee Hyunsoo's ball toss
all contributed to Park Taeo's death."
"However, it was Doyun
who delivered the fatal blow with a bat."
NAILED IT!
THE CULPRIT WAS KIM DOYUN
- I was right!
- I knew it.
"Kim Doyun's fate."
"He confessed everything
as soon as he was named the culprit."
"He was arrested
and imprisoned for murder,
but his mental state
deteriorated before the trial."
"By order of the court,
he was placed in a psychiatric ward."
- Do I need to read it all?
- It's public humiliation.
It's humiliating.
He needs to expose himself.
Why do I need to read out
everything I did?
Can't you just put this in the captions?
- Or present it as a slideshow.
- Can't I read it for him?
"It turned out to be
a bereaved family's anguished cry."
"But the law made no allowance
for the tragic circumstances."
"Due to his mental breakdown,
he was put in a treatment facility
instead of being imprisoned."
"Rather than just a murderer,
he was remembered as a victim
who lost his sister."
THE FULL STORY
22:30 THE SAINTS VICTORY
I hurt a friend in my youth.
I resolved to take baseball seriously
from that day onward.
[Jo Hajun]
Please pass this on to Lee Hyunsoo.
22:45 JO HAJUN DELIVERS THE CAKE
22:50 KANG DOHYUN THROWS AWAY
THE INSULIN AND GLUCOSE GEL
Congratulations.
22:55 KIM DOYUN VISITS THE LOCKER ROOM
Thank you.
23:00 KIM DOYUN'S MURDER ATTEMPT FAILS
COACH'S OFFICE
23:05 YOON MINSEOK
FINDS A REPORT
ABOUT HIS SON'S DEATH
23:05 LEE HYUNSOO ENTERS
We need to talk, Park Taeo!
[pants, groans]
Let's talk later, Hyunsoo.
I want to talk now!
I said let's talk later.
Are you looking down on me?
[grunts]
23:30 YOON MINSEOK
ENTERS THE LOCKER ROOM
[phone rings]
Did you deliver the cake?
Yes, it's been delivered.
An article's going to run
about Park Taeo's upcoming marriage.
He's dated her for a year.
23:35 DOYUN LEARNS TAEO CHEATED
23:40 HE GOES BACK
TO THE LOCKER ROOM
[Taeo] My blood sugar level is low.
Bring me the glucose gel from my bag.
Hey.
Do you know why Doyeon died?
No, I don't.
You don't?
Translated by Hannah Og Nam